<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--*********************************************************************
 * @author	Kingsley U. Uwode II, contractor via Robert Half Technologies
 * @since	May 28 2015
 * @link	mailto:kingzmeadow@hotmail.com
 *
 * step_05:
 * Event Waiver (*.html view companion file)
 *-->

<step id="05">
    <page_title>
        <english><![CDATA[Waiver and Release of Liability]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Renonciation et dégagement de responsabilité]]></french>
    </page_title>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Waiver and Release of Liability]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[Renonciation et dégagement de responsabilité]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[PARTICIPANT AGREEMENT, WAIVER & RELEASE OF LIABILITY 2017]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I wish to participate in OneWalk to Conquer CancerTM benefitting Alberta Cancer Foundation, scheduled to take place on June 24, 2017, as well as various pre- and post-event activities (including, without limitation, one or more training walks) (the "Event") and I agree to abide by all rules, regulations, and event instructions of the Event, as well as all applicable municipal and provincial laws and regulations.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I understand that participating in such an event, using public streets and facilities, and the use of and participation in services made available to participants during the Event (including massage, chiropractic, and medical services) is a potentially hazardous activity and can result in serious personal injury or death. I am aware of and expressly assume all risks associated with participating in this Event, including, without limitation, falls, contact with other participants, objects, bicycles and vehicles, the effects of weather, traffic, and the conditions of the streets and routes used by the Event, and I assert that my participation in this Event is voluntary.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[In consideration for being permitted to participate in this Event, I, for myself and for anyone entitled to act on my behalf, hereby waive and release, from any and all claims for injuries and/or damages I may have arising out of the Event or my participation in the Event, OneWalk to Conquer Cancer, CauseForce, LLC, CauseForce Canada, Inc., the Alberta Cancer Foundation, the Alberta Cancer Board, the Province of Alberta, Canada, Canada Lands Company CLC Limited and its property managers, any beneficiaries, sponsors, officials, participating clubs, communities, organizations, friends of the event, Walkers, Crew Members, participants, third-party vendors, government or public entities (including, without limitation, the various departments of transportation), and each of their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, predecessors, officers, directors, employees, volunteers, agents, and representatives, including, without limitation, the Event medical sponsor, medical director, and members of any medical team which provides services during or after the Event (the "Releasees").]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I intend by this Agreement, Waiver & Release ("Agreement"), in advance, to waive my rights, to covenant not to sue to release for future claims, and to discharge all of the Releasees, from any and all loss or damage, including, but not limited to claims for damages for death, personal injury or property damage that I may have, or which may hereafter accrue to me, as a result of my participation in all or any portion of this Event, even though that liability may arise from negligence (whether simple or gross), carelessness, or recklessness on the part of any of the Releasees, from dangerous or defective streets, facilities, property or equipment owned, maintained, or controlled by them or because of their possible liability without fault. I further agree to indemnity the Releasees from any and all damages, costs, claims or demands (including reasonable attorney's fees and costs) made by any third party caused in whole or in part by my actions.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I understand and agree that this Agreement is binding on my heirs, assigns, and legal representatives. I attest that I am physically capable of, and have sufficiently trained for, completing each respective element of this Event. If I am aware of or under treatment for any physical infirmity, disorder, ailment, or illness, my medical care provider has been apprised of, and has approved of, my participation in this Event. I acknowledge that I, and I alone, am solely responsible for my personal health and safety, and the personal property I bring with me. I consent to receive medical treatment which may be advisable in the event of illness or injuries suffered by me during this Event, and I agree to pay for the costs of any such medical treatment.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I agree that my participation in the Event is subject to the sole discretion of the organizers of the Event, and that my participation may be limited or terminated, with or without cause. If I am under the age of 18, I understand I MUST have a guardian accompany me on the Event as a fellow, registered participant.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I understand that the Event may be delayed, postponed or canceled due to a cause or event that is not reasonably foreseeable or otherwise caused by or under the control of the OneWalk to Conquer Cancer, including without limitation, acts of God, fires, floods, explosions, riots, wars, sabotage, terrorism, vandalism, accidents, governmental acts, injunctions, strikes and other like events that are beyond the reasonable anticipation and control of the organizers.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I understand that all donations processed by the OneWalk to Conquer Cancer donation office are non-refundable and non-transferable, even if I do not participate in the Event. I further understand that my registration fee is non-refundable, non-transferable, does not apply toward my fundraising commitment, and is not tax receiptable.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[If I am a walker, I understand that I must raise at least $1,500 in order to walk in the Event. If I have not raised at least $1,500 before June 24, 2017, I may make my own donation to reach that minimum in order to walk.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I give permission to the OneWalk to Conquer Cancer, CauseForce, LLC, CauseForce Canada, Inc., the Alberta Cancer Foundation, the Alberta Cancer Board, and each of their respective affiliates, subsidiaries and agents, for the free use of my name, photograph, voice, or likeness, in any broadcast, telecast, advertising promotion, or other account of this Event or marketing or promotion for future or similar events, and waive any rights of privacy I may have in that regard, and I understand and consent that I will periodically be receiving communications related to my participation in the Event.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[THIS WAIVER AND RELEASE SHALL BE INTERPRETED AND THE RIGHTS OF THE PARTIES DETERMINED UNDER THE LAWS OF THE PROVINCE OF ALBERTA. THE ALBERTA COURTS SHALL HAVE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION FOR ANY DISPUTE ARISING UNDER, OR PERTAINING TO, THIS WAIVER AND RELEASE.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I expressly agree that this Agreement is intended to be as broad and inclusive as is permitted by law and that if any provision of this Agreement shall be found to be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this Agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>

    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I have carefully read this Agreement and fully understand its contents. I am aware that this is a release of liability and a binding contract between myself and the Releasees, and I sign it of my own free will. I understand that I am giving up substantial rights, including my right to sue. I acknowledge that I am signing this Agreement freely and voluntarily, and intend by my signature to be a complete and unconditional release of all liability to the greatest extent allowed by law.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[Enter your first and last name]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[I am at least 18 years of age and have carefully read this document, including the Waiver and Release, fully understand its contents and voluntarily agree. If under the age of 18, I have carefully read this document with my parent or guardian, fully understand its contents and participate with their consent.]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[To get a printable version of this waiver]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
    <text>
        <english><![CDATA[click here]]></english>
        <french><![CDATA[]]></french>
    </text>
</step>
